♪♪♪
[Saul]
Previously on "Homeland"...
A panel of eight generals
and four admirals
deemed that his actions
did not rise
to the level
of a capital offense.
You don't think that's a problem
for us going forward?
- Is this him?
- What did she tell you?
Nothing. I did not
tell him anything.
She told me you're ready
to testify.
Nobody's testifying.
This is Brett O'Keefe. Welcome
to Day 52 of the Resistance.
[man] Easy. Easy, Mr. O'Keefe.
You're not under arrest.
Now you said
put the country first.
I'm offering you an opportunity
to do just that.
A job, you mean?
How does National Security
Advisor sound?
You have $38,000
in credit card debt
and a variety of aliases.
You don't have a job.
Please, tell me you realize
we've been here before.
Jesus. You know, not every shred
of nonconventional behavior
boils down to an onset
of hypomania.
[car door closes]
Sorry, sir. The President
asked for bug sweeps,
home and office,
all senior staff.
Get the fuck out of my house.
Is that order clear?
♪ tense music playing ♪
[taps keys]
♪♪♪
[chains rattling]
[thud]
Aah!
[exhales sharply]
♪♪♪
[exhales deeply]
[Keane] He saved our lives.
[Carrie] Yeah.
What was his name?
[Brody]
Carrie, you're not yourself.
[Carrie] You don't have
my condition.
I'm dealing with it.
I-I've been dealing with it
since I was 22.
♪♪♪
[Maggie] She said no one at work
could know. She's bipolar.
[man] The mood of the country,
it's not great.
[siren wailing]
[O'Keefe] Civil... War.
[Carrie]
Madam President, please!
You have to put a stop to this!
[woman] It's only getting worse.
[Quinn]
Is there no fucking line?
[Hillary Clinton]
Ridiculous lies and accusations.
♪♪♪
[woman] The White House
is in crisis mode.
[Saul] We're talking
about information warfare.
[Carrie] Our country
is under attack.
♪♪♪
[O'Keefe]
The time to rise up is now!
♪♪♪
[Carrie] I swore an oath
to protect it.
[siren wailing]
[Quinn] Just think of me
as a light on the heavens,
a beacon steering you clear
of the wrongs.
[O'Keefe] An American hero died
last night.
Jamie McClendon,
three star general.
An early casualty
in our revolution.
He will not be the last.
They say he died
of a heart attack,
that he just keeled over
and died.
Nothing could be done, okay?
A heart attack.
This marine's marine
who went through six tours
of Afghanistan and Iraq
without so much as a head cold.
A heart attack.
This force of nature
who could outrun recruits
half his age...
he just dropped dead?
That's what they want us
to believe.
♪ ominous music playing ♪
Even though the prison guard
responsible for his safety
grew up on the very same block
as the President's
Chief of Staff.
That's right,
David Wellington
and that prison guard...
they grew up together.
But the General...
Oh, his heart just kinda...
[makes splatting sound]
...gave out.
You expect us to believe that?
Really?!
The President called
for his death.
The tribunal said no, but this
Hitler in the White House...
Oh! She will not be denied!
The only way to stop
this violence against us,
this violence of lies,
is to fight back
with a clenched fist of truth!
♪♪♪
[Keane] How did it happen?
[Attorney General] It appears
he had a heart attack.
So it's just bad luck.
Brett O'Keefe says
one of the prison guards
was a childhood friend
of Mr. Wellington's.
Is that true?
Not that we could establish.
It's bullshit, obviously.
That may be, but at least
O'Keefe has an explanation
for what happened, which, as far
as I can tell, we do not,
because even I don't believe
that a decorated soldier
in perfect health
suddenly drops dead
of a coronary
the moment he sets foot
in federal custody.
Why don't you get back to us,
if and when you actually
know something?
[sips]
Madam President.
[door opens]
[door closes]
You shouldn't listen
to O'Keefe.
My listening to O'Keefe
is not the problem.
Well, it is if you think
that I used someone
I supposedly knew in third grade
to off McClendon.
I don't think that.
They do, out there,
because that is what
O'Keefe is telling them.
You know what we need to do?
Change the con...
Change the conversation.
Yeah, you keep saying.
Well,
I have an idea for that.
It involves Saul Berenson...
and 200 others.
A mass release.
So they can keep
plotting against me.
Most of them were
nowhere near the conspiracy.
Most of them haven't been
adequately questioned yet.
After two months,
that's on us.
Releasing them would be
a show of good faith.
How about someone shows me
some good faith?
Not gonna happen.
That's the point.
As long as everyone who's anyone
in this town has a friend
or a colleague or a goddamn
family member behind bars,
you will get no cooperation
anywhere, no traction.
Things will only get worse.
Either you release them...
Or what?
Or what, David?
Either you release them
or get ready to incarcerate
the whole town,
because it's not just
Brett O'Keefe
gunning for you anymore.
It's everyone.
[switch clicks]
That's weird.
Right when I was
calling her Hitler
for, like, the tenth time,
I could feel myself
leave my body and float up next
to that jar of peaches there.
Brett.
Well, hello.
[footsteps ascend stairs]
♪♪♪
[cheers and applause]
Thank you!
[applause continues]
Clenched fist of truth.
[chuckles] I like that.
So do I. That's why I stole it.
[laughter]
My word.
America.
Yes, sir. And this...
First battle of the Civil War,
fought right over there.
Five miles
past the tree line.
- Philippi.
Now I was taught it was
Fort Sumpter, out at the coast.
This was
the first land battle.
June 3, 1861.
Governor of Virginia didn't
know what side he was on.
It was a state of confusion
in the people.
I'd say there's a lot less
confusion this time around,
thanks to you.
No, I-I mean it.
Show him, J.J.
Come on. Show him.
Rebel!
"Re-bel."
Holy shit, it's me!
[laughter]
I'm not utterly clueless.
I-I know.
Getting my niece involved
in my... business
was a huge lapse
of judgment.
[sighs deeply]
But I-I... [sighs]
was running out of options,
and... and... and... and...
Honestly, the whole situation
was so unique,
I can basically guarantee
that won't happen again.
And what is it?
This... this business.
Uh, it was meeting, uh,
that needed to be relocated
at the last second.
And what about
the credit card debt?
[scoffs] Was there
a segue there I missed?
I'm just trying to understand
the whole picture.
You have a home,
with your sister.
You have a place to live.
And yet, at the same time,
you're checked into
at least two expensive hotels
for I'm not sure
what purpose.
You want to explain that?
Well, obviously,
you're talking to my sister.
- Why not ask her?
- I have talked to her, yes.
- She's concerned about you.
- About credit cards?
No, not just.
She said you lost someone,
that a friend of yours...
maybe your best friend...
died violently
in front of your eyes.
Yeah. [sniffles]
You know what? He would have
understood what I'm doing.
He never let me down, ever.
He would be right here
with me now.
[sighs]
[voice breaks]
He would have gotten it.
Gotten what exactly?
[sighs]
Our country is under attack,
and I am called on...
to protect it.
Not like it's something
I feel I should do,
if I can find the time.
I mean, I swore an oath,
just like my friend did,
to do something,
to the best of my ability
to help my country,
which I am doing.
And what my sister fails
to comprehend...
[scoffs]
is that I'm making progress.
Okay.
Let me ask you.
How does that sound to you,
what you just said?
It sounds true.
And?
And I'm taking my medication,
if that's what you're asking.
- I take it every day.
- Lithium?
That's been your principal
therapy for 15 years now, right?
- Prescribed by your sister.
- Originally.
Are you aware that
in a small part
of the population,
Lithium can become ineffective
after that much time?
It simply stops working.
[buzzer, clank]
[door locks]
Good news. The President
has accepted your terms.
She's agreed to release you,
along with the 200 others,
just like you asked,
provided you accept a position
in her administration...
National Security Advisor.
Can I ask why
the sudden shift?
President had
a change of heart.
[buzzer in distance]
Was this before or after
General McClendon died?
- Does it matter?
- Yeah, David, it matters.
Because if my new position
is really shit screen
for the administration,
I'm not interested.
You'd rather have 200 people
sitting in jail?
Yeah.
First, I don't think that you
or anyone actually believes
that the President
of the United States
had a General offed
in prison.
Second, no one's expecting you
to pick up pom-poms
and become some kind of
cheerleader.
Good.
But no carping
from the sidelines either.
No press leaks undermining
the President's statements.
We want...
a partner.
We want to leave
the mess behind
and move
the country forward.
When does this happen?
This, uh, moving.
Soon as you say yes.
♪ dramatic music playing ♪
[sighs]
[exhales deeply]
[breathing deeply]
[continues breathing deeply]
♪♪♪
[taps key]
[taps keyboard]
[sighs]
[door opens on screen]
♪♪♪
Madam President.
- [Keane] You know your lines?
- Think so.
"Time to move on."
That's what my advisors say.
Thank you.
But realistically?
The national security
establishment came after me
with machine guns
as far as I can see
for no other reason than that
they felt disrespected.
I doubt I'll ever get over it.
I'm not even sure I should.
It was a very small group,
Madam President.
- You're sure about that.
- Yes.
And it never included me.
I was there that day with you,
in the lead vehicle.
My driver was killed
in the explosion.
The doctors
spent three hours
pulling broken glass
out of my face.
I was on your side.
I hope so.
[door opens]
[Wellington]
They're ready.
♪ tense music playing ♪
[typing]
[computer whooshes]
♪♪♪
[buttons clicking]
[cellphone rings]
[ring]
[indistinct conversations]
[beep]
Sorry. Gotta deal with this.
- [Carrie] Hello?
- What is this?
I'm not sure. She's... she's got
some connection to Wellington.
A colleague, maybe?
A secret girlfriend?
I meant, what the fuck
are you doing, calling me?
Look, I don't need you to do
anything except I.D. her.
Do that, and... and I'll
take care of the rest.
I-I know you're under
a microscope there.
Look, what about
our last encounter
suggested I ever wanted to hear
from you again?
I just need you to I.D. her.
It's important.
- I'm on my own here.
- And why do you think that is?
[sighs] Look... I...
[cellphone beeps]
Hello?
Dante? Are you there?
[knock on door]
- Who were you talking to?
- Nobody. [sighs]
Sorry.
I-I-I wasn't snooping.
I came up
because there's something
I think you'll want to see.
[amplified voice]
What began as an investigation
into a violent conspiracy
against the heart
of our government
has become a source
of such acrimony and division
that I've decided,
in the interest of this country,
it is time to put it behind us.
A group that has come
to be known as "The Two Hundred"
is being released today
as we speak.
[applause and murmuring]
Among those released today,
is Saul Berenson,
my new
National Security Advisor.
[applause on TV]
[Saul]
Thank you, Madam President...
Mommy, Uncle Saul's on TV!
...for this... great honor.
We cannot let recent events
derail the work of this nation.
We are still one nation.
What is this?
Her new
National Security Advisor.
Saul?
[Maggie] It's what you wanted,
isn't it? He's out.
[Saul] ...and while we squabble,
they gain ground.
While we attack our own
government, they revel
- in their good luck.
- I don't get it.
[Bill] What's to get?
Um, why he's joining them.
Well, for one thing,
because those 200 people
you've been obsessing about,
the political prisoners,
so-called?
- They're being released.
- What?
Released. All of them.
So... you were wrong.
The President
is not a dictator.
The world is not coming
to an end.
[Maggie] Shh. I wanna hear this.
By the end of the day,
they will all be released...
an event that you swore
wouldn't occur
during in our lifetimes.
Let's see
if it actually happens.
Most of them are already out.
[scoffs] They never should've
been in, in the first place.
[Bill] You never admit
you're wrong, do you?
♪♪♪
[Saul, amplified voice]
...what the mass release shows
is that the system works.
[people asking questions
at once]
Yes?
What about
your own incarceration?
Are you saying now
that it was justified?
What's important is not that
I was in, but that I'm out,
standing in front of you.
It's testimony
to the open-mindedness
of this administration...
[lowered voice]
Have you told him?
[lowered voice] Not yet. Wanted
to see how he did on this first.
[Saul] ...to addressing
the many security challenges
this country is facing
around the world.
- [all shouting at once]
- Yes, sir?
What will be your first order
of business?
Finding my office. Thank you.
[scattered laughter, applause]
Well,
they didn't lynch me.
You did well. Thank you.
So? What next?
David will get you started.
What's that mean?
It's what the reporter
was asking,
your first order of business.
[Saul] I have some thoughts
on that.
Well, so does the President.
She feels it's important
to send the right message,
- to the country.
- What sort of message?
Well, we have a very troubling
national security situation
that's grown more and more
out of control.
What has?
O'Keefe.
Okay, wait.
- We just announced an amnesty.
- Not for him.
He was working directly
with Dar Adal.
So was I. You just made me
National Security Advisor.
Saul, he's been thumbing
his nose at an arrest warrant
for six weeks, calling for
the overthrow of the government.
The President's questioning
the FBI's commitment
to bring him in at all.
It has to stop.
Since when is domestic police
work in my job description?
We see this
as hunting a terrorist.
President trusts you.
She wants you in charge.
Good night, beautiful girl.
Mmm. [kisses] Sleep tight.
- You okay?
- I like it here.
So do I.
Then why are you mad
all the time?
Hmm?
Like yelling at Uncle Bill.
Oh, I wasn't yelling, sweetie.
We just... disagreed.
You always disagree.
I'll try to be nicer.
Okay?
I don't want to have
to leave here.
I don't know where we'd go.
Oh, sweetheart, is that what
you're worried about,
where we'd go?
Listen to me.
This is our family,
yours and mine.
We don't have to go anywhere.
All right?
♪ somber music playing ♪
[whispers] I love you,
Franny Banany.
Mmm. [kisses]
Now get some sleep.
Night.
[switch clicks]
♪♪♪
[door squeaks closed]
[sighs heavily]
[exhales deeply]
[switch clicks]
♪♪♪
[taps key]
[laptop chimes faintly]
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
[laptop chimes]
[typing]
[taps key, laptop whirring]
[Franny] Mommy!
- Oh!
- Help.
Oh, sweetie,
you missed a button.
Here.
[laptop whooshes]
What's wrong?
Uh, nothing. Why don't you, uh,
go start your breakfast?
I'll be down in
a second, okay? Okay.
♪ suspenseful music playing ♪
[taps key]
♪♪♪
[exhales deeply]
[Maggie] Carrie?
Carrie, can you please
come down?
♪♪♪
Hey. What's going on?
My meeting got moved
an hour earlier,
so can you take the girls
to school?
- [Josie] I can do it.
- [Maggie] No. So, Carrie?
Um... [sighs] I wish I could,
but I-I have an interview.
- [Maggie] Drop them on the way.
- [Josie] I can do it.
[keys jangle]
No.
[Carrie] It's on Skype,
in about ten minutes.
Looking like that?
Um, I-I'm about to change.
I'm sorry.
So I either reschedule
my meeting again,
or I take her right now.
She ready?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, she's ready.
[Maggie] Okay, Franny.
Let's go, sweetie.
Have a good day at school.
All right, munchkin?
- Mwah. [kisses] Love you.
- Good luck.
The interview.
Yeah, thanks. And thanks.
[Maggie] Yeah.
Come on, girls, let's go.
[door closes]
♪♪♪
Fuck!
[sighs]
[gunshots]
[laughing]
No better feeling,
is there?
Exercising
your constitutional rights.
- You wanna try?
- I'm good.
You're gonna want to.
Uncle Dan...
he's got a surprise.
[laughing]
- That is hilarious!
- I told you you'd want to.
[laughs]
Well, why the hell not?
You know what people forget?
The Second Amendment isn't
about needing guns for hunting
or... or target shootin'
or security.
No, sir. It's about
Resisting Tyranny.
The Founding Fathers,
in their infinite wisdom,
foresaw the dark day
when we would face
a President like Keane,
as deadly
as any foreign king.
And we would have to fight
for our lives and liberty
all over again.
[gunshot]
Uhh! [grunts]
- Are you okay?
- [exhales sharply]
Did I hit her?
[laughter]
It was a frame grab
off the surveillance cams.
Some guy on 4chan said
he recognized her,
had another photo.
I clicked without thinking.
So incredibly stupid.
[sighs deeply]
Lately, I don't know.
It's just been
one fucking thing
after another.
[laptop whirs]
[sighs deeply]
Well?
Your keyboard's locked and all
your files are encrypted.
Yeah, no, I got that.
But how bad is it?
It's bad. The malware uses
elliptic curve encryption.
- But you can fix it, right?
- No.
- You can fix anything.
- Not this.
Nobody has been able
to crack this, not yet anyway.
[huffs] Well,
what am I supposed to do?
You know I can't go
to the police.
What's on that hard drive could
put us both in prison.
There's only one option.
What?
You have to pay the ransom.
[sighs]
I'm broke, Max.
I'm... I'm worse than broke.
Borrow money
from your sister.
I can't. I'm already
on thin ice with her.
I can loan you $753.
[sighs]
But, look, Carrie,
you really
don't have any other choice.
You have to pay it.
[deep male voice]
The loser's right.
♪ tense music playing ♪
And... the price just doubled.
It's now ten grand.
♪♪♪
[inhales deeply]
Tell the loser to leave.
Leave, Max,
or the price doubles again.
[door closes]
[sighs]
Okay. He's gone.
- Just you and me then.
- What do you want?
Oh, I'd say
it's pretty obvious.
[sighs] Well, if you've seen
my bank statements,
you know I'm overdrawn
on every single account.
You're white, college-educated,
living in America.
You'll figure something out.
And you've got 24 hours.
At least give me
until next week.
No. No extensions.
- Please.
- If you're not ready
to transfer $10,000 in Bitcoin
tomorrow at this time,
I'm publishing the contents
of your hard drive online.
Make for some
very interesting reading,
don't you think?
Hmm? See ya.
Hey! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no, no! Come back!
[tapping keys]
Fuck!
[breathing heavily]
[telephone rings]
Hello?
Yeah, hold on.
- Paley's here.
- About fucking time.
- Are you sure about this?
- Positive.
Send him in.
[receiver clatters]
Madam President.
- David.
- Thanks for coming in, Sam.
Of course.
How about we start with
your home state, Senator?
You want to tell me
what exactly's going on?
Happy to. It's all hype,
Madam President.
Oh, I don't think so.
You've got armed civilians
patrolling the border.
They're harmless. Yahoos.
In open violation of
a U.S. District Court Order.
Believe me, Arizona Border ReCon
isn't about to lead a revolt
on the federal government.
[inhales sharply]
Well, it doesn't help
that you're all over
the local media down there,
calling me un-American,
weak on national defense,
warning me not to visit
anytime soon.
"I'm afraid we can no longer
guarantee her safety."
Well... maybe I did get
a little...
- carried away there.
- No shit.
Why don't we all sit down?
No, let's not, David.
The senator won't be
staying long.
Not unless he's willing
to shut down
his committee's investigation.
Excuse me?
As of this morning,
everybody swept up
in the second wave of arrests
has been released.
Most are back at work
already.
Releasing them
doesn't change the fact
that they were
unlawfully detained.
And that's not
the only sin of commission.
What are you talking about?
There's the very strange timing
of General McClendon's
heart attack...
- You're not serious.
- ...coming, as it did,
right on the heels
of your very unusual appeal
for the death penalty.
You're not gonna dignify
that nonsense with hearings?
I have a sworn duty,
Madam President, just like you.
Like hell you do.
We can ask nicely, Senator,
or we can go to war
with you
next November.
Next November, huh?
Arizona's going
majority-minority any day now,
and our polling indicates
you're 50-50
to lose your seat
as it is.
The White House weighs in,
all our resources,
you're toast.
You think so?
I know so.
Honestly, come next November,
I don't think I'm the one
out of a job.
Madam President.
[door opens and closes]
[exhaling deeply]
♪ tense music playing ♪
[exhales deeply]
♪♪♪
[tapping keys]
Hello?
I'm here. I...
I wanna talk.
[taps key]
[whispers] Fuck.
[normal voice] Hello?
[taps keys]
[laptop whooshes]
Hello?
[electronic chirp]
Hey, what the hell?
Since when is it 20 grand?
What is going on?
[taps key]
[scoffs]
Hey! Hey, are you there?
[taps keys]
[deep male voice]
Yeah. I'm here.
I had until tomorrow. You... you
can't keep changing the terms.
No, that's the beauty of it.
I can do whatever I want.
- No, it's not fair.
- Oh, boo fucking hoo.
[sighs]
Seriously, 20 grand is
too much to ask.
I'm not sure the President's
Chief of Staff would agree.
What did he do?
Did he dump you or something?
Break your heart?
[scoffs] I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Don't play dumb.
You're a freak.
You got cameras all over
his house, in his bedroom.
[chuckles] Bet you were
hoping I didn't notice, huh?
It's too bad you and the loser
let it slip.
And now you're gonna be
my golden goose.
[laughs]
What the hell is
so funny?
- Go ahead.
- Go ahead what?
Well, tell him.
I don't give a shit.
- Don't think I won't.
- [sighs]
He knows already.
How else do you think
I got the cameras in there?
He gets off on it,
me watching him.
You're lying.
I'm not. [scoffs]
David Wellington likes to party.
Google him sometime.
Do it now.
[typing sound]
Five years ago,
NYPD Vice busted him
with a couple of escorts
in a suite at the Waldorf.
Photos got out online.
It ended his career.
[typing stops and starts]
Well?
You believe me now?
[sighs] Maybe.
Doesn't change the fact
I still own your hard drive.
[sighs]
Doesn't change the fact
that I still can't afford
to pay you.
[exhales slowly]
You seeing this?
[man] Yeah.
So what if I'm a freak?
[man] What do you mean?
♪♪♪
You interested?
[deep male voice]
What've you got in mind?
[inhales deeply]
I don't know.
An exchange of services?
[man] Like what?
Anything you want.
I want...
you to take off your shirt.
Not now. Later, in person.
[deep male voice] I said,
take off your fucking shirt!
[sighs]
Now sit back. I wanna see.
Take off your bra, too.
♪♪♪
[man inhales sharply]
Okay. [exhales deeply]
Now play with your titties.
♪♪♪
Use both hands.
[ragged breathing]
Now... roll your nipples.
Make 'em long and full.
[man gasping]
That's it. That's it.
[exhales deeply]
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't stop!
It's not for free, asshole.
You want more, it has to be
in person.
And you have to unlock
my computer.
♪♪♪
♪ tense music playing ♪
[indistinct conversations]
[knocks]
[police radio chatter]
[electronic chirps]
[indistinct conversations]
[horn blaring, tires screeching]
- Fuck you, feds!
- [crowd laughing]
[tires screeching]
[cheers and applause]
♪♪♪
[indistinct conversations]
[Maslin] Berenson.
Special Agent in Charge
Sean Maslin.
I hear
you were close this time.
Yeah. They got word we were
coming, snuck him out.
- Who's "they"?
- Local law enforcement.
- They say where they took him?
- No, not yet.
[sighs]
What happened to his face?
[Maslin] Resisting arrest.
Refused to accept that
my agents had jurisdiction.
Honestly, the shit we have to
wade through down here.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
I want to talk to 'em.
- Okay.
- On my own.
Uncuff 'em,
get 'em something to drink.
Split 'em up.
- Ouch! Careful.
- You're so full of shit.
The great defender
of the Second Amendment
never fired a gun
in his life.
- I have.
- You're such a liar.
I did. Summer camp,
40 years ago.
Hold this.
I'm gonna ask one of the guys
to drive me to town today.
There's a bus station there,
and I'll show you how to log on
for the broadcast.
- It's not that complicated.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's going on? You said you
wanted a bed, which you got,
and clean clothes and a shower,
which you also got.
- You look great, actually.
- Stop. I told you, I'm done.
- I need to go home.
- To what?
My life.
You'd trade all this for
a studio apartment in Brooklyn?
Yeah. I don't like being
surrounded
- by gun-toting crazies.
- That's why you gotta stay,
protect me
from the lunatic fringe.
[knock on door]
Uh, Dad says food's ready.
Thanks, J.J.
We'll be right there.
Hey, J.J.! Hold on.
J.J.! You...
you heard us talkin'.
- It's none of my business.
- Oh, it is your business.
I've been on the run
for nearly 60 days,
and the only reason the Feds
haven't caught up with me
is because of the courage and
kindness of families like yours.
I was having trouble in there
with the world's worst
girlfriend,
and I said something
I'm not proud of.
- It's okay.
- It's not okay.
I ask your forgiveness.
Do you...
think we're crazy?
Anyone who stands up
for what they believe,
people are gonna say
they're crazy.
They've been calling me that
for years.
But what you and your daddy
have made here
is the very opposite
of crazy.
It's blessed.
I'm proud to be fightin'
on your side.
[both chuckle]
[police radio chatter]
I was speaking
to your colleague.
it was interesting.
You think I don't know
what you're doing?
Split us up, tell him
one thing, tell me another.
I'm a cop,
you fucking moron.
It was interesting
because I couldn't
find the words to express...
...to express the dismay I feel
at what I saw outside...
Hundred people,
ordinary decent citizens,
staring at the FBI
with hatred in their eyes
like they're
an occupying army.
Aren't they?
You know where
I've seen this before?
Some of the most fucked-up
places on the planet,
places we're so proud
we're not...
Iraq, Afghanistan, Syria.
Locals facing the armies
of governments they hate.
All it takes is one wrong word,
one wrong move,
and people start dying.
Get the Feds to leave,
the folks will go home.
The FBI won't leave
without O'Keefe.
Then you got a problem.
No, you got a problem.
That's what I'm saying.
These are your people,
people you swore to protect.
You're leaving them out there
in harm's way.
I know Brett O'Keefe.
He knows me.
Tell me where you took him.
I'll go talk to him.
Alone.
I will end this.
No one will get hurt.
You have my word.
[train horn blowing]
[bell clanging]
[engine turns off]
I'm on Demoines. Parked.
[shifts gears]
[deep male voice] Get out.
Walk back in the direction
you came.
[unbuckles seat belt]
Where are you?
Start walking.
[keys turn in ignition]
[keys jangle,
door handle clacks]
[deep male voice]
Leave the bag.
Leave it.
[thud]
And the jacket.
The jacket.
[car alarm chirps]
[indistinct conversations]
- I know where O'Keefe is.
- Fantastic. All right, listen,
get Hammett in here.
I wanna be in the room...
I am going to talk to him
on my own.
- He's a federal fugitive.
- I'm aware.
Yeah? And you think, what,
he'll just turn himself in
without a fight?
Look, I'm not letting you make
the same mess you made here...
pissing off the locals, beating
up a cop, for fuck's sake?
One call to the Director,
you're off the case.
We go together...
then it's O'Keefe and me.
Agreed?
[sighs]
♪ suspenseful music playing ♪
[deep male voice]
On your right.
[man]
It's the green door.
[man] It's open.
[door creaks]
♪♪♪
[deep male voice]
Go left.
♪♪♪
[man] Keep moving.
[deep male voice]
Open it.
Go left.
♪♪♪
[deep male voice]
Past the tables.
Keep walking.
[deep male voice] Stop.
[deep male voice]
Don't need the phone anymore.
Put it down.
♪♪♪
Where are you?
- Okay, now you're scaring me.
- [man] Stop talking.
♪♪♪
Take off your shirt.
First unlock my computer.
Take it off.
You said you would
unlock my computer.
Why the fuck do you think
you're here?
[exhales deeply]
Take it off.
Do it now,
or I walk outta here
and I start fucking up
your life.
♪♪♪
Come on. Come on.
It's stuck.
[exhales sharply]
Turn around.
[exhales deeply]
[breathing heavily]
♪♪♪
- [grunts]
- Aah!
- You fuck!
[grunting]
- [chomps down]
- Aah!
[grunts]
[clank]
[panting] All right.
All right?
No! Aah! Aah!
[man grunting]
Unlock my computer.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[screams]
[whack]
Aah!
Unlock my computer,
or I will fucking kill you.
Aah!
Okay! It hurts!
I don't give a shit. Do it.
[whimpering]
[cellphone chimes]
Keep fucking typing.
[breathing heavily]
[laptop chirps]
♪♪♪
It's done.
Yeah?
[breathing heavily]
I swear.
[cellphone chimes]
[whispers] Please.
Please, let me go.
- Like you let me go?
- Uhh!
[smack]
Aah! [groans]
I'm CIA, you motherfucker.
You try anything,
I will hunt you down.
I will kill you.
- I know who you are...
- [groans, grunts]
...where you live.
I've got your prints, your DNA,
- your ugly fucking face.
- [grunts]
I've got you for the rest
of your life. Do you hear?
[gasping]
[gagging]
[grunts, gasps]
[grunts]
[gasps]
♪♪♪