Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN: He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe and
the Middle East.
PRESIDENT GEORGE H.W. BUSH: This will not
stand, this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN: This relentless
pursuit of terror.
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH:
We will make no distinction...
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next samba
we're going to swing for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
...until something stops him.
CARRIE: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking Arabic)
SAUL:
What the fuck are you doing?
Fuck!
CARRIE: I missed
something once before.
I won't...
I can't let that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something
that day.
CARRIE:
Everyone's not me.
Previously on Homeland...
Suicide bomber almost blew up
Vice President Walden.
He made a tape.
My name is Nicholas Brody.
So you want to follow Brody?
Surveillance equipment,
a few good men.
And Carrie.
But I'm sending you a guy.
Peter Quinn.
Brody has a meeting
this morning
at the CIA, and we want
to throw him a jolt.
Which is you.
Are you back here?
Yeah, in a way.
Carrie Mathison was at the CIA.
Renew the relationship.
Could be useful, actually.
I'm sorry for all
you went through.
I mean, fucking ECT?
Where'd you hear that?
Was it terrible?
No.
He made me.
PETER: No way.
He's on his way up to his room.
He's acting totally normal.
We have to go in.
He's on to me.
Your work is done tonight.
Get the fuck back here.
SAUL:
Oh, what is she doing?
It reeks, you know.
You still have your twisted
theories about me, don't you?
Not theories anymore.
Get down, get down now!
You're a disgrace
to your nation,
Sergeant Nicholas Brody.
You're a traitor
and a terrorist,
and now it's time
you pay for that.
(heavy door slams)
- David...
- Not a word.
(keypad beeping)
What the hell happened?
I thought this was
a surveillance operation.
It was until Carrie
took it upon herself
to break cover and confront him.
We had no choice
but to move in.
She says Brody made her.
- Did he?
- No.
It's possible. I don't know.
Neither does he.
What I do know is we've got
to get Brody
to tell us what he knows
before Nazir's people
realize he's missing.
I agree.
I figure we got 24 hours, tops.
After that, you have to figure
they go to ground or
pick a new target.
And we lose our best shot at
stopping an attack on America.
So, who goes in there
and talks to him?
Carrie.
Are you shitting me?
She knows Brody better
than anyone here.
She's the only one who knows him
up close and personal.
She is way too emotional,
reckless.
I don't know
what they've told you,
but Brody made me, I swear.
I had no choice.
Peter's going to
take a whack at him.
With all due respect, David,
that's a mistake.
You can go home now.
Let her stay.
She can help.
She's forgotten more
about Brody and Nazir
than we'll ever know.
But, Carrie, this
is Peter's show.
Clear?
I'll run interference
on Brody's office.
(door closes)
I should be in there, Saul.
You're lucky you're
in the building.
You're in the custody of the
Central Intelligence Agency.
I'd like to ask you
a few questions.
I'm a United States congressman.
You can't just kidnap me
and shackle me
to the fucking floor.
Actually, we can.
Thanks to you and your
colleagues in congress,
we have fairly broad powers
to detain and interrogate.
Look, I've been
down this road before.
I'm not what Carrie says I am.
Ask David Estes--
he'll tell you.
By Carrie, you mean
Carrie Mathison?
Yes.
And what exactly does
she think you are?
A terrorist.
And you're not?
No, I'm not.
You should know that everything
that you say in here
will be used against
you in your trial.
You should also know
that you are facing a
possible death sentence.
- I want a lawyer.
- Well, life is full of disappointments.
I want a fucking lawyer!
(Brody breathing heavily)
After your capture in 2003,
you were subjected to
a period of five years
of profound and
constant torture.
(sighs) It says here,
(clears throat)
"Brutally beaten, electricity,
isolation and worse."
Am I getting things
right so far?
It is important
that we're accurate.
(panting) Hmm?
Hmm.
Why did the torture stop?
I'm completely
off the grid here, aren't I?
Why did the torture stop?
I don't know.
Who was Issa?
Issa? Issa was one of my guards.
I told Carrie that already.
Was he the reason
the torture stopped?
I have no idea.
Were you aware
that Abu Nazir's youngest
son was also named Issa?
I didn't know that, no.
You've never met the boy?
No.
Were you aware that he
was killed at his madrassa
during an American
drone strike?
I wasn't, no.
Hmm.
He's setting the table
with Brody's lies.
He's good.
PETER:
In your debrief, you indicate
that you have never
met Abu Nazir.
Yet Carrie Mathison's addendum
to your file contradicts that.
Well, she's lying.
Why would she do that?
Because she's
out of her fucking mind.
Because she's obsessed with me.
PETER:
Is it also a lie that
while in captivity,
you converted to Islam?
Yes.
Do you have any idea why,
on the morning of December 17,
Thomas Walker shot and
killed Elizabeth Gaines?
I assume it was because
he was trying to kill
the vice president.
- So he missed?
- Apparently.
The best shot in your unit?
It happens.
You want to hear my theory?
My theory is Elizabeth
Gaines was killed
in order to instigate
Secret Service protocols,
which it did.
Everybody was herded together
into the State
Department panic room
without security checks.
27 of our best and brightest,
all crowded on in
there with you,
who was wearing a bomb.
A...
Where the fuck
would I get a bomb?
So you weren't wearing a bomb?
No.
You didn't know Abu Nazir's son?
And you did not conspire
to assassinate the
vice president?
Of course I didn't.
I've got something
I'd like you to watch.
(papers rustling)
My name is Nicholas Brody,
and I'm a sergeant in
the United States Marine Corps.
I have a wife
and two kids,
who I love.
I'll be right back.
By the time you watch this,
you'll have read
a lot of things about me,
about what I've done.
That's why I wanted
to explain myself.
(door closes)
So that you'll know the truth.
On May 19, 2003,
as part
of a two-man sniper team
serving
in Operation Iraqi Freedom...
Let him suck on that.
Neatly done.
When the tape ends,
we'll let him stew for a while.
No sleep.
...where I was held captive
for more than eight years.
What hotel?
I'm not sure.
For how long?
Are you guys getting a divorce?
No, we're...
we're just giving each other
some breathing room.
What does that mean?
It means we're trying
very hard to work things out.
Work what out?
Our problems.
(sighs)
I'll see you
guys at 5:00.
It's pizza night.
Is Dad really coming back?
Yeah, he's coming back.
How do you know?
Because I know, Chris.
Hey.
Hi.
Are you okay?
Who broke his heart?
My mother.
What'd she do?
Throw away his Xbox?
No, she, uh, threw our father
out of the house.
Oh.
My mother does
that once a month.
My dad sleeps in the
guest wing for a week,
she swears she's done
with him for good,
next thing I know,
they're drinking martinis and
listening to My Fair Lady.
(chuckles)
My therapist says it's
pretty common, but...
You have a therapist?
(chuckles) I had a therapist.
Once.
So, um,
I talked to Xander.
Home guy?
Yeah, well,
the former home guy.
Oh.
Take me out tonight?
Okay.
How about a movie?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Once Upon a Time in America
is playing at Dupont Circle.
Sergio Leone.
I have absolutely no
idea who that is.
(chuckles)
He's a great Italian filmmaker
who specializes
in wide-screen agony.
GREG: What do you mean, he's
not answering his phone?
He has to answer his phone;
he's a congressman.
He can't just disappear.
What about his wife?
She's not answering, either?
Jesus.
Greg Merriles, did I
pronounce that right?
- Yes.
- My name is David Estes.
I work for the Central
Intelligence Agency.
I know who you are, sir.
Congressman Brody is
helping us out on a matter
of national security.
He is?
It's imperative that no one,
including his family,
questions his absence.
How long will he be helping you?
- A few days.
- A few days?
That's going to be tricky.
His-his schedule's jam-packed.
Committee meetings,
uh, interviews galore.
He's at the vice president's
beck and call.
I think the safest thing would
be to say that he has the flu.
There's a nasty strain
going around right now.
Tell anybody who asks
he's staying at the Ashford.
Why would he be staying
at the Ashford?
He and his wife are in
the middle of a conjugal spat.
That's actually the truth.
It is? Huh.
Why don't I know that?
Just reassure her
that he's fine,
that his doctor has seen him
and that all will be well.
Call me if there's a problem.
Hey, this is Nicholas Brody.
Please leave a message.
(beep)
Brody, it's me.
Call me back.
(door opening)
Listen to this.
JESSICA:
Brody, it's me again.
Please call me back.
The kids are freaked.
I'm freaked, to be honest.
We need to talk.
She's called three times.
So, what do you
say we start over?
Who was Issa?
Abu Nazir's son.
Not your guard?
- No.
- In fact, you knew Issa.
He was your student.
You taught him English.
Yes.
And you came to love him
as if he were your own son.
Yes, I did.
PETER:
He was killed in a drone strike
ordered by the highest levels
of government.
(sighs)
He was killed in a drone strike
ordered by the vice president
of the United States.
Who you called a war criminal.
- Because he is.
- Truth is,
you returned from captivity
in Iraq intent on killing him.
Yes.
Which is why,
on the morning of December 17,
wearing a suicide vest,
you conspired to get yourself
next to the vice president
in the State Department
panic room.
No.
What do you mean, no?
I wasn't wearing a vest.
I made a tape. That's all.
You're lying to me again.
BRODY:
I was fucked-up.
I was angry.
But ask yourself,
what really happened?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Tell that to Elizabeth Gaines
and the two Secret Service
agents who lost their lives
on the steps
of the State Department.
I had nothing to do with that.
Do you really expect anyone
to believe that
after watching this?
Believe what you want.
No bomb went off.
I killed no one.
You've got nothing on me.
No real evidence at all.
Do you really want to do this?
What?
This.
Play games.
Because I can play, too.
What do you think Jessica
will say
when I show her your confession?
I think she'll be glad
I didn't go through with it.
I think she'll understand
that I was unhinged
by everything
that's been done to me,
everything I've been through.
She's a very
understanding woman.
And... Dana?
Is she as understanding?
What about Chris?
How old is he now?
12?
What do you think the rest
of their lives will look like?
My dad, the jihadist murderer.
I'll take my chances.
Go ahead and show them.
We know Abu Nazir
is going to hit us
in retaliation
for Israel's bombing
of Iranian nuclear sites.
You were part of his American
terrorist cell.
No, I wasn't.
When is the strike
going to occur?
I don't know.
What's the target?
(sighs)
I don't know.
What... is the target?
(screaming) That jog your
memory, you fucking asshole?
Jesus fucking Christ!
When's the attack?! (gasps)
Talk, you motherfucker!
You will talk to me,
Brody, goddamn it.
Get the fuck off of me!
What the fuck
is the matter with you?!
This is my interrogation!
Get him out of here.
Brody, I will fuck you.
Fuck you!
(panting)
- We should go.
- No, I'm not going anywhere.
(gasps, yells)
(Brody gasps, Carrie sighs)
(panting)
I can do this, Saul.
It's my turn.
(Brody groans)
(panting)
I'm sure he isn't here.
He hasn't been around
since yesterday.
- I just want to see for myself.
- Of course.
Yesterday.
Hi, Betsy. Is Greg there?
(phone rings) What's up?
I'm at the Ashford.
No Brody, no flu.
I even brought him
chicken noodle soup.
Ugh. Not there? Really?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
So where is he?
Well, don't worry.
I'll find him.
You do that,
and you tell him to call me.
As you can see here,
here and here,
Israeli jets weren't able
to penetrate the deeper bunkers.
(cell phone buzzing)
The Iranians hardened the roof
with reinforced concrete,
and then they covered it with...
Estes.
She knows.
Who is this?
Greg Merriles.
Jessica Brody is all over my ass
looking for her husband.
She knows I'm bullshitting her.
Uh, we need a little more time.
Let me speak to Brody.
He's busy right now.
I'll wait.
I'll have him call you back.
(phone beeps off)
Fuck.
(door opens and closes)
You broke my heart, you know.
Was that easy for you?
Was that fun?
Because of you,
I questioned my own sanity.
I had myself committed
to a mental institution.
I lost my job, too.
I lost my place in the world.
I lost everything.
I just told Estes the truth.
You were harassing my family.
The truth? Bullshit.
You came this close to blowing
him into a million pieces.
Did you tell him that?
I didn't wear a bomb.
(panting)
Did you even think about me
when you went to Estes?
Tell me you at least felt a...
a pang of regret,
a teeny little sliver of guilt.
You said before that
I'm obsessed with you.
You really think that?
Yeah, I do.
So it's a one-way street?
You have no feelings for me?
Go ahead. I'm a big girl.
I can take it.
Come on, Brody.
Look me in the eye and
tell me you felt nothing
up in that cabin.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
(laughs)
"Hurt" doesn't quite cover it.
So did you? Did you...
did you feel anything?
Oh, for Christ's sake, Carrie,
we were playing each other.
No, I wasn't.
Not the whole time, anyway.
I-I remember thinking
I was exactly where I belonged.
I know what you're doing.
And it's not going to work.
I'm just happy
to be talking to you again.
Are you thirsty?
(sighs)
Water, please?
What you did with the knife,
losing your temper--
that was all theater?
Wasn't it?
Every good cop needs a bad cop.
(sighs)
What the fuck is she doing?
Just listen.
(whispers):
Alone at last.
CARRIE:
Here, let me get these off you.
(Brody sighs)
(sighs)
(long sigh)
Can I ask you something?
I have a choice?
You said up at the cabin that
you didn't have
anyone to talk to.
Did you... did you
ever find anybody?
A friend?
A therapist?
No.
You never went back to that
support group, did you?
- No.
- Why?
I don't know.
(long sigh)
People always ask
me about the war.
You know...
was it as bad as everyone says?
I-I never know
what to tell them.
(laughs) "My interpreter
was burned alive and
then hung from a bridge"?
No one survives intact.
No.
Do you still have nightmares?
(sighs) Sometimes I
shake uncontrollably
for no reason at all.
So what do you say...
when people ask you what
it was like over there?
As little as possible.
But if they insist?
I lie.
Tell them stories
they want to hear.
It's the lies that undo us.
It's the lies we think
we need to survive.
When was the last time
you told the truth?
About five minutes ago
when I said I didn't
wear a bomb.
You never wore a bomb?
No.
But you did make
a suicide tape.
Who did you give it to?
I didn't give it to anyone.
I threw it in the trash.
And yet it wound up in Beirut in
a Hezbollah commander's house?
See? You're
drowning in lies.
I'm surprised you can even
keep them straight anymore.
Walden lied to the
whole fucking world
- about the drone strike!
- Yes, he did.
But you're not
like him, are you?
- You're not a monster.
- No.
Are you sure you're
not a monster, Brody?
I'm sure.
But Abu Nazir is.
His pattern is to target
innocent civilians
and inflict mass casualties.
Kenya, 1998, a
busy marketplace.
Madrid, 2004, a packed
commuter train.
Last spring, a department
store in Amsterdam.
He doesn't strike soldiers
and high-ranking
murderers like Walden.
He kills wives...
and children.
Danas and...
Chrises and Jessicas.
I know that you think
that he was kind to you,
that he saved you,
but the truth is...
he systematically pulled
you apart, Brody...
piece by piece
until there was
nothing left but pain.
And then he relieved the pain
and he put you back together
again as someone else.
He gave you a boy to love,
and then that other
monster, Walden,
took that boy away.
Between the two of them,
they made your life a misery.
Wouldn't it be a
relief to stop lying?
For instance, if
I stopped lying,
I could say to you, "Brody...
I want you to leave
your wife and children
and be with me."
(laughs)
There, I said it.
I'm still alive.
It feels good.
Try it.
You're a good man, Brody.
You're a good man...
...because you didn't explode
the vest you were wearing.
Right?
(whispers):
I wasn't wearing a vest.
You decided not to
kill those people.
You decided to let Walden live.
Even Walden.
Dana called you, didn't she?
CARRIE: While you were there
in the panic room with Walden.
She used my cell.
What did she say?
She asked me to come home.
I said I would.
And I did.
It was hearing Dana's voice that
changed your mind, wasn't it?
(pants)
She asked you to come
home, and you did.
Why?
Maybe because...
Maybe because you
suddenly understood
that killing yourself
and ruining Dana's life
wouldn't bring Issa back.
Maybe because you knew then
how much you loved
your own child.
Maybe because you were
just sick of death.
That's the Brody
I'm talking to.
That's the Brody that
knows the difference
between warfare and terrorism.
That's the Brody I met
up in that cabin.
That's the Brody
I fell in love with.
What is Abu Nazir's plan?
I don't know.
But there is a plan, right?
To attack America?
Yes.
Who does know the plan?
Uh, Roya Hammad, maybe.
I'm not sure.
Roya Hammad?
Who gave you the suicide vest?
A tailor from Gettysburg
in Pennsylvania.
What's his name?
Bassel something.
Is there anyone else
in Nazir's network
that you've had contact with?
There was Afzal Hamid.
Al Zahrani, the...
Saudi attaché.
(sighs) And Tom Walker.
All dead.
(whispers):
(exhales)
(long exhale)
(door opens)
We need you to call your wife.
Reassure her that you're okay.
That you'll be home...
later tonight.
When's Finn picking you up?
Soon.
Are you excited?
It's just a date, Mom.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Brody.
Just checking in.
How are you?
Where have you been?
Looking for some answers.
Did you find any?
Yeah, I think so.
How are the kids?
They miss their father.
We need to talk, Brody.
I'll come by the house.
When?
Tonight.
Jess, don't worry.
We're going to be fine.
(beep)
Your father's coming home.
Sure he is.
SAUL:
Okay.
Easy.
(panting)
(groans)
(insects chittering, chirping)
Well, you look nice.
I combed my hair.
Well, then you look beautiful.
Did you tell Xander
you're seeing Finn?
Yeah, I-I told him.
I figured it would just be
too creepy otherwise.
Or just be wrong otherwise.
I'm proud of you.
It is kind of weird, though.
I mean, me dating
the boss's son.
It's not weird at all.
Anyway, Vice President Walden
isn't Dad's boss exactly.
They're colleagues.
Mmm.
I'm sorry about
all the confusion.
I know your dad and I are
supposed to be the grown-ups.
It's... whatever.
Dad changed over there.
They did something to him.
They did.
(car approaching)
There he is.
Hi, Mrs. Brody.
Hi, Finn.
Get her back safe and sound.
Yes, ma'am.
(door locks)
(gasps)
Brody, we need
to go over your options.
Here's what you're facing...
a trial with all
the attendant publicity,
followed by
a long prison sentence.
You'll bring dishonor
and shame to yourself,
the Marine Corps,
the country and your family.
Or...
you help us,
and all of that goes away.
Help you how?
We send you back into the world
as if nothing happened.
You help us figure out
what Abu Nazir's plan is.
No trial?
No charges, no trial.
Jess and the kids?
They'll never know.
You quit politics,
move to the town of your choice
somewhere far, far away.
Immunity?
You guys don't have the
power to give me that.
You better hope we do.
♪ ♪
You okay?
Let's have some fun.
Hmm, fun.
You want to have some fun, huh?
(tires squealing) Oh, shit!
(tires squealing, horns honking)
(laughing)
Yeah!
Faster.
- Faster!
- Okay. All right.
Yeah! Okay.
(laughing)
(screaming)
Stop! Finn, stop!
Oh, fuck!
You got to turn around!
You got to go back there!
- Fuck!
- Come on.
Dana, please! If anyone finds
out about this, my life is over!
Well, we at least
have to call 911!
No. They can trace the call.
See? She's fine, Dana, okay?
He's calling 911. There's
nothing we can do about it.
Finn, we almost killed someone!
Dana, I'm begging you,
let's just get out of here.
My dad is the vice president
of the United States.
(moaning):
Oh, fuck me.
Okay. Okay.
Go.
I assume you've spoken
to Roya about me.
She was the one who suggested
I reestablish the relationship.
Good.
So if she comments
on your absence,
- just tell her you were with me.
- With you?
Tell her we couldn't keep
our hands off each other.
The affair will be our
cover going forward.
If you need me
for whatever reason,
you just call and
say you miss me.
I'll do the same.
We'll meet at my apartment.
(sighs)
So Walden just stands there
and gets elected president?
He could lose.
Abu Nazir will find out
I'm working for you.
No, he won't.
Not if we're careful.
When he does,
he'll go after my family.
That's how he operates.
We'll protect your family.
(sighs)
♪ ♪
The last time
I went on a bender
was when you went to the prom
with Billy Birkbeck
instead of me.
I was 17 years old.
Where's your car?
I left it outside a bar
in Fairfax. I took a cab.
How's the flu?
Greg just made that up.
Don't blame him.
He was just doing his job.
I'd like your permission
to come home.
Okay.
But I need the truth, Brody.
That was the deal.
If you want to come back,
I need to know what is
going on with you.
And don't give me any bullshit
about a bender
and Billy Birkbeck.
No more secrets.
Can it wait until the morning?
No, it can't.
Okay.
You're going to think this
is a little crazy, Jess.
I'm working for the CIA.
The CIA?
Yep.
Doing what?
Helping out on matters
of national security.
Brody, if this is
some more bullshit...
It's not.
I swear to God.
It's the truth.
I can't tell you
any more right now.
I shouldn't have told you
this much already.
(front door opens)
You're home early.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
What happened to you?
CHRIS:
Hey, Dad.
Are you back?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm back.
Good night.
♪ ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com